<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Mac is connected to Wi-Fi but not working</title>
    <link href="/2023/05/07/Mac-is-connected-to-wifi-but-not-working/"/>
    <url>/2023/05/07/Mac-is-connected-to-wifi-but-not-working/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today my MacBook crashed. I had no choice but to restart it by pressing and holding the power button. When it was ready, I found that I couldn’t access the Internet anymore despite being connected to the Wi-Fi. I tried the self-diagnosis but to no avail. After some troubleshooting, I found a way to refresh the Wi-Fi setting by simply deleting and recreating it. To do so, open the network tab and right-click the Wi-Fi in the System Settings, then choose to delete the Wi-Fi service. Then click the button at the bottom (with three dots on it) to create a new Wi-Fi service. That’s it. Hopefully, your network will be restored.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>[object Object]</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Start to learn German</title>
    <link href="/2023/05/06/Start-to-learn-German/"/>
    <url>/2023/05/06/Start-to-learn-German/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Recently, I have been learning German. I have learned some of the basic words and sentences.I hope to continue learning it.</p><p>As a native Chinese speaker, it’s not easy for me to get used to a completely different language like German.There are hardly any similarities between these two languages. Luckily, I am capable of speaking essential English thanks to compulsory education in China, so I can manage to learn German through English.</p><p>I have found Duolingo to be an easy way to start. However, if I want to delve deeper into it, I will need to find another method. I have heard that DW is an app to learn German more seriously and systematically. I will give that a shot.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>personal</tag>
      
      <tag>language</tag>
      
      <tag>germany</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>My first blog</title>
    <link href="/2023/05/05/My-first-blog/"/>
    <url>/2023/05/05/My-first-blog/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I decided to start a blog today.</p><p>This post is for test only.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>gossip</tag>
      
      <tag>personal</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
